# ROHIT SEHGAL

13432 Lakeshore Drive Clive, IA

Cell - (515)-724-2794

Personal - rohitbsehgal1998@gmail.com

Personal site - rohitbsehgal.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**

I am High School student at Valley High School, in West Des Moines, Iowa. I am interested in Computer Science and Engineering. I started learning to program in 2013 when I was 14 years old. Since then I have learned many new programming languages, and have been to a few hackathons. Along side programming I like wrestling, lifting, and gaming in my freetime.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Intern(Developer), Webspec Design

Des Moines, IA — May 2014 - June 2015

As a Developer at Webspec Design My job was to create websites using HTML5, Javascript, and CSS. Along side making websites I had to keep them up to date with updates to their wordpress, and small changes that clients requested.

### Accomplishments

- Learned how to work closely with other developers, designers, and project managers.
- Became much more advanced with PHP and Javascript.
- Learned about responsive websites and SEO.
- Learned to work closely with Git.

#### Cashier/Server, Mcdonalds

Des Moines, IA — October, 2013 To March, 2014

My job as a cashier/server at Mcdonalds was to operate the cash register, and make/serve food to customers.

# Accomplishments

- Handle Cash Register
- Cook and serve
- Learned to work closely with a team

# **EDUCATION**

# **Valley High School**

Diploma — 2014-Current

I am a student at Valley High School, in West Des Moines, Iowa. I take classes that interest me, but are also challenging. I also wrestle for Valley at 145 lbs.

## **SKILLS**

Advanced:

Objective-C, Swift, HTML, SASS/CSS, Javascript

Intermediate:

Wordpress, PHP, Java, Git

Beginner:

Python, Hardware, SQL, SEO